<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/mywebsite/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/mywebsite/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2026-02-28T09:03:34-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mywebsite/feed.xml</id><title type="html">My Site</title><subtitle></subtitle><entry><title type="html">A Day in Indianapolis, Indiana</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mywebsite/2026/02/26/a_day_in_indianapolis_indiana.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Day in Indianapolis, Indiana" /><published>2026-02-26T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2026-02-26T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mywebsite/2026/02/26/a_day_in_indianapolis_indiana</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mywebsite/2026/02/26/a_day_in_indianapolis_indiana.html"><![CDATA[<p>Indianapolis is one of those cities that quietly impresses you. It’s clean, welcoming, walkable, and full of history, food, and fun experiences. From fascinating museums to canal strolls, pedal pubs, monuments, and legendary steakhouses — Indy delivers a full day of adventure.</p>

<h2 id="morning-at-the-indiana-state-museum">Morning at the Indiana State Museum</h2>

<p>I started my day at the Indiana State Museum, located in a beautiful and lively section of downtown Indianapolis. The museum sits inside White River State Park, which makes the entire area feel open, scenic, and energetic.</p>

<p>The museum itself is fascinating. It dives deep into Indiana’s natural history, cultural development, science, industry, and more. Every exhibit feels thoughtfully curated and immersive. You can easily spend hours exploring and still feel like there’s more to discover.</p>

<p>One of the best parts? When you walk outside, you’re immediately connected to the scenic Downtown Canal Walk.</p>

<h2 id="strolling-the-downtown-canal-walk">Strolling the Downtown Canal Walk</h2>

<p>The Canal Walk is one of my favorite parts of Indianapolis. It offers a peaceful, relaxing stroll with beautiful water views — but it’s more than just scenery.</p>

<p>Along the path, you’ll find the powerful USS Indianapolis National Monument. The monument tells the tragic story of the USS Indianapolis, its sinking during World War II, and the harrowing shark attacks that followed. It’s sobering, moving, and important history to reflect on.</p>

<p>The canal also connects to the White River and continues through White River State Park, linking to several other museums and attractions — including the nearby Indianapolis Zoo.</p>

<p>If you’re not in the mood to walk, you can rent a pedal boat or even hop into a gondola for a romantic ride along the water. It’s a unique way to see downtown from a different perspective.</p>

<h2 id="afternoon-fun-with-the-hangar">Afternoon Fun with The Hangar</h2>

<p>Later in the afternoon, I highly recommend heading to The Hangar — especially for their famous HandleBar Pedal Pub Tour.</p>

<p>Yes, it’s exactly what it sounds like.</p>

<p>You and a group hop onto a giant multi-person bike, pedal together, sip drinks, and get an entertaining tour of downtown Indianapolis. It’s energetic, hilarious, and a fantastic way to experience the city. If you’ve ever wanted to drink beer while powering your own moving bar through the streets of Indy — this is your chance.</p>

<h2 id="exploring-monument-circle">Exploring Monument Circle</h2>

<p>One thing I truly appreciate about Indianapolis is how pristine and well-managed downtown feels. Many cities struggle to keep their downtown areas clean and vibrant — but Indy does it right.</p>

<p>In the heart of downtown sits the iconic Soldiers and Sailors Monument. This towering monument honors the soldiers and sailors from Indiana who were lost in war. It’s both beautiful and meaningful.</p>

<p>Around Monument Circle, you’ll find a lovely public space where people gather, relax, and play games like bag toss. The surrounding area is filled with shops, restaurants, and local businesses.</p>

<p>If you’re looking for something refreshing, I recommend stopping by KOKO TEA for an amazing boba tea. It’s the perfect sweet treat while exploring downtown.</p>

<h2 id="dinner-at-a-legendary-steakhouse">Dinner at a Legendary Steakhouse</h2>

<p>To cap off the day, there is one place you absolutely must visit: St. Elmo Steak House.</p>

<p>This legendary steakhouse is famous nationwide — and for good reason. The steak dinner I had there was quite possibly the best I’ve ever experienced. From the quality of the meat to the impeccable service, everything felt classic and elevated.</p>

<p>The restaurant was even featured on the hit TV show Parks and Recreation, further cementing its place in pop culture.</p>

<h2 id="why-indianapolis-surprised-me">Why Indianapolis Surprised Me</h2>

<p>Indianapolis is beautiful, clean, and full of character. Between its rich history, relaxing canal walks, engaging tours, lively downtown atmosphere, and incredible dining scene, it offers something for everyone.</p>

<p>Whether you’re into museums, outdoor strolls, unique group experiences, or unforgettable meals — Indy delivers.</p>

<p>It’s a city full of things to see, do, eat, and drink — and it absolutely deserves a spot on your travel list.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indianapolis is one of those cities that quietly impresses you. It’s clean, welcoming, walkable, and full of history, food, and fun experiences. From fascinating museums to canal strolls, pedal pubs, monuments, and legendary steakhouses — Indy delivers a full day of adventure.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Day In Cleveland, Ohio</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mywebsite/2026/02/25/a_day_in_cleveland_ohio.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Day In Cleveland, Ohio" /><published>2026-02-25T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2026-02-25T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mywebsite/2026/02/25/a_day_in_cleveland_ohio</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mywebsite/2026/02/25/a_day_in_cleveland_ohio.html"><![CDATA[<p>There’s something special about spending a full day exploring a city from sunrise to sunset — and my day in Cleveland was packed with great beer, great food, football, shopping, live music, and a perfect Lake Erie sunset.</p>

<h2 id="morning-at-great-lakes-brewing-company">Morning at Great Lakes Brewing Company</h2>

<p>I started my day bright and early at the legendary Great Lakes Brewing Company. As one of Cleveland’s most iconic craft breweries, it was the perfect way to kick off the morning.</p>

<p>The tour was both fun and educational. I got to learn about the brewing process — from selecting quality ingredients to fermentation and bottling — and hear the story of how this brewery helped shape Cleveland’s craft beer scene. Of course, the best part was sampling several of their craft beers. Each pour had its own personality, from crisp and refreshing to bold and complex.</p>

<p>Right next door is their brewery-owned restaurant, which serves an incredible breakfast. The food was absolutely delicious, and enjoying fresh draft beer alongside a hearty morning meal made for a uniquely Cleveland experience.</p>

<h2 id="game-time-at-huntington-bank-field">Game Time at Huntington Bank Field</h2>

<p>After a relaxing and flavorful morning, I headed downtown to Huntington Bank Field, home of the Cleveland Browns.</p>

<p>The energy around the stadium was electric. Browns fans are passionate, loyal, and loud — and the atmosphere did not disappoint. Watching the Browns take the field with Lake Erie in the background is something every football fan should experience at least once. Even better? The Browns won! There’s nothing like celebrating a home-team victory surrounded by thousands of cheering fans.</p>

<h2 id="afternoon-at-legacy-village">Afternoon at Legacy Village</h2>

<p>After the game, I took a short drive to Lyndhurst to explore Legacy Village.</p>

<p>Legacy Village has a great mix of shops, from clothing boutiques to unique specialty stores and food spots. The outdoor layout makes it especially enjoyable to walk around, and I was lucky enough to catch some live music while browsing. It’s the kind of place where you can easily spend hours just soaking in the atmosphere.</p>

<p>While there, I stopped at Black Box Fix, a unique Black-owned business specializing in Creole and Cajun-inspired sandwiches. Their menu is bold, flavorful, and unlike anything you’ll find at a typical sandwich shop. I ordered one of their incredible creations — packed with spices, sauces, and serious personality.</p>

<h2 id="sunset-on-lake-erie">Sunset on Lake Erie</h2>

<p>To end the day, I took my sandwich to the shores of Lake Erie.</p>

<p>Sitting on the beach, enjoying that Cajun sandwich while watching the sun dip below the horizon, was the perfect close to a full Cleveland day. The sky turned shades of orange, pink, and purple, reflecting off the water in a way that makes you slow down and appreciate the moment.</p>

<p>From craft beer and football to shopping, live music, and a lakeside sunset, Cleveland delivered an unforgettable day. If you’re ever looking for a city that blends food, sports, culture, and waterfront beauty — Cleveland should absolutely be on your list.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s something special about spending a full day exploring a city from sunrise to sunset — and my day in Cleveland was packed with great beer, great food, football, shopping, live music, and a perfect Lake Erie sunset.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Anheuser-Busch Brewery Tour</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mywebsite/2025/12/20/anheuser-busch_brewery_tour.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Anheuser-Busch Brewery Tour" /><published>2025-12-20T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2025-12-20T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mywebsite/2025/12/20/anheuser-busch_brewery_tour</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mywebsite/2025/12/20/anheuser-busch_brewery_tour.html"><![CDATA[<p>If you’re a fan of beer, history, or just a good time, the Anheuser-Busch Brewery tour in St. Louis should definitely be on your list. I recently went on their Day Fresh tour, and it was an absolute blast from start to finish.</p>

<p>One of the first highlights? The famous Anheuser-Busch Clydesdales. Getting up close to these majestic horses in their stables was incredible—there’s something about seeing these gentle giants in person that photos just can’t capture.</p>

<p>The tour itself was about an hour and a half, and it covered everything from the brewing process to the packing and bottling lines. I loved seeing how a massive operation like this works behind the scenes, and the buildings on the campus are impressive, to say the least. The guides were friendly and shared fascinating tidbits about the history of Anheuser-Busch and its founders, which made the experience feel both educational and fun.</p>

<p>Now, for the best part: the samples. I got to try several beers, but the real standout was the “St. Louis Lager”, a vintage recipe that had been lost for decades. This exclusive brew is only available seasonally, and it was amazing to taste a piece of history that’s rarely seen outside the brewery. To top it off, they even gave us a freshly bottled beer to take home at the end of the tour—what a cool touch!</p>

<p>At just $15 for the tour, it was totally worth it. I’ve been on a few brewery tours before, but this one might just be my favorite. Between the historic vibes, the incredible marketing flair (looking at you, Clydesdales), and the tasting experience, it really felt like a perfect blend of fun and education.</p>

<p>If you find yourself in St. Louis and love a good beer story, the Anheuser-Busch Brewery tour is a must-visit. Cheers!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re a fan of beer, history, or just a good time, the Anheuser-Busch Brewery tour in St. Louis should definitely be on your list. I recently went on their Day Fresh tour, and it was an absolute blast from start to finish.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Fort Worth Stockyards</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/mywebsite/2025/10/12/fort_worth_stockyards.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Fort Worth Stockyards" /><published>2025-10-12T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2025-10-12T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mywebsite/2025/10/12/fort_worth_stockyards</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/mywebsite/2025/10/12/fort_worth_stockyards.html"><![CDATA[<p>If you’re looking for a place where the Old West still kicks up dust, the Fort Worth Stockyards is it. Located just north of downtown Fort Worth, this historic district is full of Texas charm, longhorn cattle, and some surprisingly great coffee.</p>

<h2 id="morning-jitters-in-the-best-way">Morning Jitters (In the Best Way)</h2>

<p>My day started with a much-needed caffeine fix at Avoca Coffee Roasters, a local favorite that quickly won me over. Their Bourbon Butterscotch Latte was smooth, sweet, and had just the right kick to get me going. But the real standout? A drink called the Charlie Sheen. Yes, you read that right. It’s a cold brew mixed with Coca-Cola—odd, refreshing, and unexpectedly addictive. It’s the kind of thing you try as a joke and then find yourself low-key craving later.</p>

<h2 id="hat-fitted--feeling-it">Hat Fitted &amp; Feeling It</h2>

<p>With caffeine coursing through my veins and a bounce in my boots, I wandered into Maverick Fine Western Wear. If you’re in the market for a proper cowboy hat, this is the spot. The staff didn’t just sell me a hat—they fit me for one, making sure it matched my head shape and style. Their customer service was seriously top-notch. I walked out feeling like I could star in a Western (or at least look the part).</p>

<h2 id="exploring-the-strip">Exploring the Strip</h2>

<p>The Fort Worth Strip runs through the heart of the Stockyards and is packed with quirky shops, rustic saloons, and western boutiques. It’s the kind of place where you can pick up handcrafted leather goods, snap a pic with a longhorn, and overhear stories from real-deal cowboys—all in the span of an hour.</p>

<h2 id="longhorns--rodeo-dreams">Longhorns &amp; Rodeo Dreams</h2>

<p>One of the coolest things about the Stockyards is the twice-daily cattle drive. Real Texas cowhands guide a herd of longhorns down Exchange Avenue, and it’s as Instagram-worthy as it sounds. I made sure to catch the afternoon drive, which felt like stepping straight into history.</p>

<p>And speaking of cowboy culture, I capped off my afternoon by seeing my first-ever rodeo at the Cowtown Coliseum. Between the bull riding, barrel racing, and electrified crowd, it was an adrenaline rush like nothing else. The energy is contagious, and even if you’ve never been to a rodeo before, you’ll find yourself cheering like you grew up on a ranch.</p>

<h2 id="honky-tonkin-at-billy-bobs-texas">Honky Tonkin’ at Billy Bob’s Texas</h2>

<p>After sunset, I headed to Billy Bob’s Texas, proudly known as the world’s largest honky tonk. It’s more than just a country bar—it’s a whole experience. Think live music, dance floors, pool tables, and even indoor bull riding. Whether you’re two-stepping with strangers or just soaking up the scene, Billy Bob’s is the perfect way to end a Fort Worth night.</p>

<h2 id="final-thoughts">Final Thoughts</h2>

<p>The Fort Worth Stockyards isn’t just a tourist attraction—it’s a living piece of Western history. From custom cowboy hats and cold brew curiosities to cattle drives and country beats, this place has a little something for everyone. Whether you’re a city slicker or a wannabe cowboy like me, you’ll find something to love in Fort Worth.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a place where the Old West still kicks up dust, the Fort Worth Stockyards is it. Located just north of downtown Fort Worth, this historic district is full of Texas charm, longhorn cattle, and some surprisingly great coffee.]]></summary></entry></feed>